A Guide to the Fairfax County Office of Public Affairs Photograph Collection, 1962-2009
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 1: Negatives, 1964-1971
  - Registrar - Registering and 18 year olds - Cheryl McGinness, Assistant Registrar, registers Mr. and Mrs. Roderick Thonen to vote, 1971 July 20 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Schools - Belle View School, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Schools - Bren Mar Park Elementary School (negs for composite photo of front of building), 1969 August (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Schools - Bren Mar Park Elementary School [under construction], 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Schools - Cameron School, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Schools - Cameron School, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Schools - Cameron School, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Schools - Cardinal Forest Elementary School, Undated (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Schools - Franconia School [Lincolnia School], 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Schools - Lawrence M. Watts, Superintendent of Schools sworn in by F.W. Franklin Goodin Jr, Undated (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Schools - Legato School moved [aerial from Massey Building], 1971 March 31 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Schools - Mount Eagle School, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Schools - Mount Eagle School, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Schools - Quander Road School, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Schools - Quander Road School, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Schools - School Board Building, 1969 September 19 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Schools - School Bus [undergoing repairs], Undated (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Schools - William Cullen Bryant Intermediate School, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Schools - William Cullen Bryant Intermediate School, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Sewer - County-City sewer contract - Mayor John Russell, William S. Hoofnagle, Joseph Alexander, Donald R. Bowman, Martha V. Pennino, W. Rembert Simpson, 1971 February 2 (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Sewer - Lower Potomac Sewage Treatment Plant, 1970 September (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Sewer - Lower Potomac Sewage Treatment Plant - Accotink turn over, Undated (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Sewer - Lower Potomac Sewage Treatment Plant - Board Visit - Joseph Alexander, Anton Sparr, Donald R. Bowman, M.H. Klegerman, Donald Stevens, J. Kelley Paull, 1970 March 11 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Sewer - Lower Potomac Sewage Treatment Plant - Groundbreaking, Undated (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - Sewer - Lower Potomac Sewage Treatment Plant - Groundbreaking with Babson, Undated (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Sewer - Lower Potomac Sewage Treatment Plant - Interior-lab, Undated (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Sewer - Sewer Pumping Stations - Belle View and Belle Haven Road, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - Textures - Wood Grain curtains etc, Undated (Box 2, Folder 177)
  - Transit - Jalex(?) and Harris with model Metro car, Undated (Box 2, Folder 178)
  - Transit - McEnearney, Wright, Majer with Shirley Express Bus, Undated (Box 2, Folder 179)
  - Tysons - Tysons Corner Shopping Center, 1970 June (Box 2, Folder 180)
  - Tysons - Tysons Corner Shopping Center - model, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 181)
  - USS Fairfax County - Captain Gerald Kuhn, Carl W. Porter, Cdr. John F. Neese, Undated (Box 2, Folder 182)
  - USS Fairfax County - Carl W. Porter, Undated (Box 2, Folder 183)
  - USS Fairfax County - Carl W. Porter, Undated (Box 2, Folder 184)
  - USS Fairfax County - Carl W. Porter, Undated (Box 2, Folder 185)
  - USS Fairfax County - Cdr. John F. Neese, Vadm Luther C. Heinz, Carl W. Porter, Capt. Richard C. Fay commander Lbeach Naval Shipyard, Undated (Box 2, Folder 186)
  - USS Fairfax County - Commanding officer's reception: Vice Admiral Luther C. Heinz, Mr. and Mrs. Carl W. Porter, Cdr. & Mrs. John F. Neese, Undated (Box 2, Folder 187)
  - USS Fairfax County - Gift of National Steel and Shipbuilding Co. San Diego, California: Ship's Portrait in oil. Vice Admiral Luther C. Heinz (principal speaker), Cdr. John F. Neese (Commanding Officer), Carl W. Porter, Representatives of National Steel & Shipbuilding, Undated (Box 2, Folder 188)
  - USS Fairfax County - Right: Cdr. John F. Neese (commanding officer) Left: Carl W. Porter, Undated (Box 2, Folder 189)
  - Water Authority - Occoquan Water Treatment Plant - Groundbreaking - Fred C. Morin and Water Authority Members, 1970 August (Box 2, Folder 190)
  - Water Authority - Water Authority and Brazilian visitors, 1969 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 191)
  - Welfare - Foster Child (Do not publish this photo without obtaining release from Margaret Putnam, Welfare), Undated (Box 2, Folder 192)
  - Welfare - Foster child -Ward of Welfare Department kills time in temporary foster home while hoping permanent foster arrangements will be made soon. (Photo made for July 7, 1969 news release. No publication release is necessary for this child)., 1969 July 7 (Box 2, Folder 193)
  - Welfare - Foster children, 1969 July (Box 2, Folder 194)
  - Welfare - Moving, 1969 September 12 (Box 2, Folder 195)
  - Welfare - Tea for Ed Sterling - L to R: Edward W. Sterling, Carlton C. Massey, Mrs. Shirley Driver, 1970 December 16 (Box 2, Folder 196)
- Series 2: Photo/Negative File, 1971-1973
  - Annandale - Poor Zoning, Undated (Box 3)
  - ASAB, 1973 January (Box 3)
  - Board of Supervisors - Alan Magazine / Warren Cilkins / Jean Packard / Ethel Register Clerk, Undated (Box 3)
  - Board of Supervisors - William Hoofnagle Swearing-in, 1971 December (Box 3)
  - Board of Supervisors - William Hoofnagle Farewell, Undated (Box 3)
  - Board of Supervisors - Jean Packard - Swearing-in; Office; County Tours, 1973 January (Box 3)
  - Board of Supervisors - Supervisor Harris, 1972 January (Box 3)
  - Board of Supervisors - Hoofnagle and Magazine, Undated (Box 3)
  - Board of Supervisors - Jack Herrity, Undated (Box 3)
  - Board of Supervisors - Audrey Moore, 1971 December (Box 3)
  - Board of Supervisors - Rufus Phillips, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Board of Supervisors - James M. Scott, 1971 December (Box 3)
  - Board of Supervisors - Final Session of 1971, 1971 December (Box 3)
  - Board of Supervisors - Bradley Tree Planting, Audrey Moore and Jack Herrity - Kings Park Library, Undated (Box 3)
  - Board of Supervisors - Tree Planting, Martha Pennino, Undated (Box 3)
  - Computer/Data Systems - Interactive Terminal Facility (ITF) for school and student use, 1971 October 20 (Box 3)
  - Computer Room Tour - Data Systems, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Communications Directory - Copying Machines, 1973 January (Box 3)
  - Crossroads Center / Supervisors Lunch /Crossroads Bus, 1971 October 20 (Box 3)
  - Consumer Affairs - Director Fred Kramer, Undated (Box 3)
  - Courthouse - Old Fairfax County Courthouse, 1972 January (Box 3)
  - EAC - Kelly - Golf Trophy - EAC Offices, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Edsall Fire Station, Undated (Box 3)
  - Erosion - Response Staff, Undated (Box 3)
  - Fire Services Contract Signing, 1973 June (Box 3)
  - Fire Services - Iranian, 1972 May (Box 3)
  - Garage, 1972 April (Box 3)
  - General Services - Clifford Gaskins mailroom boss, Undated (Box 3)
  - Governmental Centers - West Springfield / Mason, Undated (Box 3)
  - Groundbreaking - Franconia, 1972 May (Box 3)
  - Health Department - Air Pollution Testers on Route 50, Undated (Box 3)
  - Health Department - School Nurses, Undated (Box 3)
  - History Commission / Spring Bank /Huntington Subdivision, 1972 February (Box 3)
  - History Commission - Preservation program, Undated (Box 3)
  - Hospital/Mental Health - Mount Vernon Hospital Groundbreaking, 1973 January (Box 3)
  - Housing - Housing and Community Development agreement with Herndon, Undated (Box 3)
  - Housing Authority - Reston Groundbreaking, 1972 September (Box 3)
  - Jane's Junk Dogs, 1972 January (Box 3)
  - Juvenile Court Project, McLean, 1973 March (Box 3)
  - Library - Nursing Home - Kings Park Library, 1971 November (Box 3)
  - Library - Kings Park Library - Children, 1973 February (Box 3)
  - Massey Building - Cafeteria, Undated (Box 3)
  - Massey Building, Undated (Box 3)
  - Massey Building - Security, 1973 May (Box 3)
  - Mental Health - Mount Vernon Center Dedication and Woodburn / Myra Coates and Simon Auster, Undated (Box 3)
  - Mental Health - Northern County Mental Health Center Groundbreaking, 1972 January (Box 3)
  - McLean Community Center - Deed and Groundbreaking, 1973 February (Box 3)
  - Onthank Awards 1974, Undated (Box 3)
  - Onthank Awards 1971, 1972 April (Box 3)
  - Orientation, 1972 April (Box 3)
  - Park Police - EAC Golf Tournament, Undated (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Castillo, County Attorney; Health Department; Mildred Bailey, Undated (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Castillo; Stern-Knudson; Stollberg; Gooding; Rothrock, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Justice Poff, Undated (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Castillo the fireman; Stern; M. Ferguson, Undated (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Lang Keith/J. Rick; Maintenance - Voting Machines; George J. Kelley 50th birthday; Janet, Response Staff, Anderson, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Telephone Course; Ted Jensen and Larry Clark; Cavanaugh/Momson; Castillo, 1971-1973 (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Dr. Miller, Blood Bank, Flu Shots, 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - Personnel - County Executive; Harman; McDonald; Blake; Reid; Hutchison - Official shots of executives, etc., 1973 July 1 (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Finz, Undated (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Deputy Executive Wilson; Morril and Secs. Assorted personnel, 1971 October 20 (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Castillo; Wilson, 1973 May (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Wilson; Mary Douglas; Housing Authority; Assessments, 1971 November (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Jentch/ Kay Scott, 1971 December (Box 4)
  - Personnel - James Reid, Undated (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Mike Long; Blake; Hutchins, 1973 (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Richard Henry; John Yarmechuk; Captain Carl Porter, 1971 October 13 (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Minority Recruiting, Undated (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Hickock; Seaton Daugherty; Budget & Management - Stern; Planning Commission; Inspecting Radio, 1972 January (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Harman; McDonald, 1973 May (Box 4)
  - Personnel - Castillo, Undated (Box 4)
  - Pine Ridge Beautification, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Planning Commission and staff - Nancy Shand(?) Planning Commission sworn in, Shiva Pant, Undated (Box 4)
  - Planning - PLUS Meetings, Undated (Box 4)
  - Planning - PLUS Meetings 1974, Undated (Box 4)
  - Planning Workshop Tysons, 1973 April 8-9 (Box 4)
  - Planning - Land Use Workshop - TV, Undated (Box 4)
  - PLUS - Frelich(?), Undated (Box 4)
  - PLUS - meetings and people, Undated (Box 4)
  - PLUS - people and meetings, 1973 (Box 4)
  - Press - Tom Love, 1972 September (Box 4)
  - Public Affairs - Gil Shaw, Undated (Box 4)
  - Print Shop - Charlie Garris and Dave Gough - Bigger Certificate - VPI Program - Dog Licesnses - Chilton Bike, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Proclamations, etc., Undated (Box 4)
  - Proclamations - Don Stevens cert; 1972 Cancer Month, Voters Registration, Undated (Box 4)
  - Proclamations/Commendations, Undated (Box 4)
  - Proclamations - Boys Clubs, Salvation Army, YWCA, Senior Citizens, 1973 (Box 4)
  - Proclamations - Cystic Fibrosis, 1972 August (Box 4)
  - Proclamations - Wolf Trap, 1973 June (Box 4)
  - Public Works - Newington, 1972 August (Box 4)
  - Public Works - Landfill Stump Axe - Litter Creeper, 1972 April (Box 4)
  - Public Works - Lorton Landfill, 1972 August (Box 4)
  - Public Works - Lorton Landfill - Mark's Colonels, Undated (Box 4)
  - Purchasing, Undated (Box 4)
  - Recreation Department - Larry Fones, Undated (Box 4)
  - Rec-Schools, 1972 April (Box 4)
  - Research and Statistics Office - Ralph Young and Computers - Canadians visit VDIS (ORS), Undated (Box 4)
  - Social Services - Christmas Gifts, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Social Services - Route 7 and Route 50 traffic - Seven Corners [Seven Corners Shopping Center area], 1972 (Box 4)
  - Schools/Herndon Project - School buses, Senior Citizens, Edison Track Team, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Sewers - Westgate Wastewater Treatment Plant, Eugene Kazmierczak, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Solid Waste, 1972 April (Box 4)
  - Sully Plantation - FCCA, 1971 October 13 (Box 4)
  - Skyline Collapse, 1973 March (Box 4)
  - Urban Design Assistance Team (UDAT), Undated (Box 4)
  - Urban Design Assistance Team (RUDAT), 1972 (Box 4)
  - Urban Design Assistance Team (UDAT), 1972 (Box 4)
  - USS Fairfax County, Undated (Box 4)
  - Vehicle Auction, Undated (Box 4)
  - Voter Registration, 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - Water Saving, 1972 April (Box 4)
  - Youth Conservation Corps, 1973 June (Box 4)
  - Zoning - Van Dorn, 1973 March (Box 4)
- Series 3: Negatives, 1974-1978
  - Road crews cleaning trash, Promiscuous dumping, The Queen housing project at Reston, 1974 August 21 (Box 5)
  - Mrs. Packard at Lyceum, Viennese officials view computers, Va. Zimmerman, 1974 September 11 (Box 5)
  - Frederick Wyse, 1974 October 24 (Box 5)
  - Cikins swearing-in and mug, Maxwell swearing-in, Flora Lewis plaque in rose garden, architects sketch of new jail, 1975 January (Box 5)
  - Food stamp eligibility worker, 1975 February (Box 5)
  - Animal Shelter stretcher donated by vets, 1975 February (Box 5)
  - Martha Pennino, 1975 February (Box 5)
  - Audrey Moore (by Charles Baptie), 1975 February (Box 5)
  - Mailroom mails expanded Agenda, 1975 February (Box 5)
  - Becky Martin legal secretary winner, 1975 February (Box 5)
  - Groveton Nutrition Project, 1975 February 21 (Box 5)
  - Dedication, John Marshall Branch Library, 1975 February 23 (Box 5)
  - Insurance Week, Bren Mar Royaltones, 1975 February 24 (Box 5)
  - Loudoun County Attorney, 1975 March (Box 5)
  - I-66 Sanitary Landfill Recycling Complex, pine seedlings, seagulls, 1975 March (Box 5)
  - Don Hughes, Weights & Measures inspector in Grand Union, West Springfield and Exxon next door (Keene Mill Road), 1975 March 2 (Box 5)
  - Col. W.W. Smith Jr., design review award winner; Flora Johnson and Supervisors, 1975 March (Box 5)
  - Simplex installs fire annunciator, Nenna and Rappelea(?) sworn in with Election Board in attendance, phone operator Audrey Rerlon retires, Nutrition Week, Larry Clark, Boardaides, Forewell, 1975 March 2 (Box 5)
  - NACO & EPA officials, Wilson and Packard, 1975 March 6-7 (Box 5)
  - Week of Young Child (Day Care), Walk for Mankind organizers and Jean Packard, Mrs. Pennino's wood cut, 1975 March 7-11 (Box 5)
  - Red Cross Month, Alan Magazine portrait, 1975 March 10 (Box 5)
  - AIDS waterless toilets, Mount Vernon Hospital topping-off, 1975 March 10-11 (Box 5)
  - Jean Packard buys first auto decal, DeMelay Week, Pennino outside, Avis Bell new human rights director, 1975 March 17 (Box 5)
  - Garden plot at Nottoway Park, Vienna residents preparing soil, 1975 March 31 (Box 5)
  - Wilton Woods wall hanging, Magazine portrait, Volunteer Recognition Week, 1975 April 14 (Box 5)
  - Old land assessment records moved out of courthouse attic, 1975 April 15 (Box 5)
  - Ted Parson plumbing inspector and corroded gas pipe at site of Reston leaks, Southgate Square, 1975 April 17 (Box 5)
  - Secretary Week, 1975 April 21 (Box 5)
  - SERV fire truck at Jefferson Station, 1975 April 25 (Box 5)
  - Landfill opens as softball diamonds, Older Americans Week, Beta Sigma Phi Week, 1975 April 27-28 (Box 5)
  - Lin Quitmeyer of Consumer Tip Fame and microphone, Savings Bond Drive, Melpar, Treasury officials and Wilson and Packard; Consumer Awareness Month; Council of Arts Membership Month, 1975 May 5-6 (Box 5)
  - Head Start Week, Jean Packard mugshot, 1975 May 12-13 (Box 5)
  - Poppy Days, Oakton Jazz Lab Band at Massey Building, Kings Park Library Talking Book Depository, 1975 May 16, 1975 May 19 (Box 5)
  - Jean Packard and air pollution emission test, 1975 May 22 (Box 5)
  - Ms. Shouse commended, Edmendson appointed student on school board, 1975 June 9 (Box 5)
  - Economic Development Authority, Polling at North Springfield precinct, Animal Shelter and family adopting, 1975 June 10 (Box 5)
  - A&I campaign toast by supervisors, William Whitesides check from Kiwanis Club, 1975 June 16-17 (Box 5)
  - Harman mugshot new Planning Director, Walter Monasch(?), 1975 June 23 (Box 5)
  - Doug Harman (2nd try), First Virginia Regiment soldiers in dress with Harman, 1975 June 30 (Box 5)
  - Wakefield Chapel, 1975 July 11 (Box 5)
  - Cikins Tour of Gum Springs Community Center, S.B. Moon Day Care kids, 1975 July 11 (Box 5)
  - Miss Fairfax County, 1975 July 14 (Box 5)
  - Cannery at Herndon Intermediate, Needlepoint seal of Fairfax County, 1975 July 18 (Box 5)
  - HUD grant to Board, Sen. Byrd Jr., Jean Packard mugshot (for passport), 1975 July 21 (Box 5)
  - Children being bathed by Herndon firefighters hose at Chantilly Pines, 1975 July 22 (Box 5)
  - Clown Week, New jail renderings with and without Sheriff Swinson, 1975 July 28 (Box 5)
  - 4-H Fair, Jos. Baker retires from BZA, 1975 July 30 - 1975 August 1 (Box 5)
  - Evelyn Wilcox certificate, Cikins and Broadsides Exhibit, Cupola of old courthouse repair and bell, 1975 August 4 (Box 5)
  - Community Action Agency contract signing, 1975 August 8 (Box 5)
  - Ruth Gil library outreach, 1975 August 8 (Box 5)
  - Bicentennial logo winners and logo by itself, 1975 August 11 (Box 5)
  - Patterson & Earle, 1975 August 19 (Box 5)
  - Senior Citized ID/Discout kickoff, 1975 August 21 (Box 5)
  - R.D. Morrison at Little Hunting Creek sewage plant, 1975 August 22 (Box 5)
  - Bomb Scare evacuation of Massey Building, Pat McDonald on stairs, 1975 August 25 (Box 5)
  - Mount Vernon Mental Health Center (posed staff members), 1975 August 29 (Box 5)
  - Little League State Champ Central Springfield Team, Amateur Radio Week, 1975 September 8 (Box 5)
  - Monasch, Packard and international group of planners on State Department tour, 1975 September 13 (Box 5)
  - Mount Vernon Mental Health Center Dedication, 1975 September 14 (Box 5)
  - James Scott, Bastenbrook and Little League donor (Falls Church), 1975 September 15 (Box 5)
  - Hunting & Fishing Days, Fairfax County Symphony Orchestra Week, 1975 September 15 (Box 5)
  - New Animal Shelter, Senior Citizen ID card sessions at McLean Community Center, 1975 September 19 (Box 5)
  - Girls Probation House, Route 29-211, 1975 September 18 (Box 5)
  - Immunization Month, Council of Arts notepaper, Gloria Matthews, 1975 September 29 (Box 5)
  - Rufus Phillips lectures Highway Commission, 1975 October 1 (Box 5)
  - Courthouse plaque and 1844 bell in cupola, 1975 October 2 (Box 5)
  - Patowmack Canal at Great Falls with Corky Mayo of NPS, 1975 October 3 (Box 5)
  - Clara Holmes retirement (Finance Office), Georgetown Pike By-Way Trail Dedication, 1975 October 3 (Box 5)
  - Friends of Tree Awards, Rehab Loan Fund Agreement with banks, Sam Finz' birthday flowers (ORS), 1975 October 20 (Box 5)
  - Reston police station lease signing, 1975 October 20 (Box 5)
  - Craisre(?) commended on bond sale and AAA rating, 1975 October 22 (Box 5)
  - Packard and D. Stroh with PLUS plans (for NACO), 1975 October 27 (Box 5)
  - Onthank Award winners and presentations, 1975 October 29 (Box 5)
  - Anuity and Animal Welfare League at new shelter presenting check from AWL, past unidentified proclamations, ACCESS rendering, 1975 October 29 (Box 5)
  - Election Night unofficial vote counting, 1975 November 4 (Box 5)
  - Legato School donations from students, 1975 November 7 (Box 5)
  - Reconstruction Willard Health Center, Extension's entomologist and soil testing kits, 1975 November 11 (Box 5)
  - Dranesville Sup. Shacochis, Legato School in bright sun, Courthouse walkway, 1975 November 11 (Box 5)
  - ACCESS rendering, Senior shuttle buses arrive at Tysons, 1975 November 12 (Box 5)
  - EMT fire and rescue workers train at Fairfax Hospital, Cyrus Taylor school board appointee, Deaf Awareness Week, 1975 November 17 (Box 5)
  - Jim Wycoff planning commission executive director, Waynewood Women's Club check to Mount Vernon Health Center, Foreign service officers briefed by Jean Packard, D. Harman, 1975 November 21 (Box 5)
  - Warren Cikins mugshut, 1975 December (Box 5)
  - Copy negs for Travesky and Pennino, 3 proclamations, 1975 December (Box 5)
  - Patsy Fox retirement (Zoning Admin), 1975 December (Box 5)
  - Packard, Phillips, Gooding get mementoes, appraiser, Public Works build trail, Story-time at Vienna Library, "Oklahoma" cast at Lake Braddock Secondary School, 1975 December 8 (Box 5)
  - Board meets with legislator, Christmas tree at Massey Building, Magazine informed, 1975 December 15 (Box 5)
  - Packard farewell luncheon, 1975 December 18 (Box 5)
  - Rep. Harris says bye to Supervisors, 1975 December 16 (Box 5)
  - Jay Lambert to be Asst. County Executive, 1975 December 22 (Box 5)
  - Child Abuse Protection Week Proclamation, 1976 January (Box 5)
  - Harmond & Robert W. Wilson farewell, 1976 January (Box 5)
  - Jim Scott mugshot, 1976 January (Box 5)
  - Service Award Pins, Barbara Taylor passport, 1976 January 20 (Box 5)
  - Rockbridge City Quilt on display with Susan Lelville and Liz David, 1976 January (Box 5)
  - Robert W. Wilson mug for passport, Barbara Taylor, 1976 January (Box 5)
  - Robert Lundy and Avis Bell, Human Rights, 1976 January 21 (Box 5)
  - COMCAT Library microfilm catalogue, 1976 February (Box 5)
  - John Shacochis mugshot (negative from pro photographer), 1976 February (Box 5)
  - Montons Sisters in Recreation Department at Mantua Elementary School, Mrs. Watts, Ms. Smith, Ms. Skeggs of Senior Development program, county attorney plants, 1976 Februrary 7 (Box 5)
  - Planning Commission Maxwell, Pellelferil(?), Roehrs sworn in, 1976 February 11 (Box 5)
  - Judge Jamborsky sworn in on Circuit Bench (actually, he signs oath with Hoofnagle) with family, 1976 February 13 (Box 5)
  - Scott, Travesky, Engineers Week, 1976 February 23 (Box 5)
  - Manpower shots at JKJ Chevrolet, 1976 February 27 (Box 5)
  - Woodrow Wilson Library reopening, 1976 February 29 (Box 5)
  - Red Cross Month, 1976 March 1 (Box 5)
  - Boy Scouts at Board of Supervisors, 1976 March 1 (Box 5)
  - St. Mary's Catholic Church, Legato School (second shooting), 1976 March 5 (Box 5)
  - Jail Groundbreaking including Herrity, 1976 March 22 (Box 5)
  - Marshall High School Girl's Basketball Team (State Champs), DeMolay Week, Welsh Councilman visitor of Shacochis', BZA assembled with Durrer, 1976 March 22 (Box 5)
  - Plant Experts being trained by Extension at Dulles, 1976 March 25 (Box 5)
  - Pennino and Cikins with 4-H Winners, 1976 April (Box 5)
  - Microfiche of old Court Records, Blach to Watersides, Hoofnagle, 1976 April 8 (Box 5)
  - Head Start Kids visit Massey Building from S.B. Moon and Higher Horizon, 1976 April 8 (Box 5)
  - Secretaries Week, 1976 April 12 (Box 5)
  - Economic Development Authority sign bond issues agreement with Penn Mutual for AMF move into Airtronics Building, Measles shots at Willard Health Center, 1976 April 13 (Box 5)
  - Proclamations - Feeling Fine with WRC Bryson Rash, Reston School Board Committee, 1976 April 19 (Box 5)
  - Courthouse Plaque Unveiled, 1976 April 21 (Box 5)
  - Fire Service Recognition Day, Proclamations - Consumer Awareness Month, Older Americans Month, Salute to Nursing, 1976 May 3 (Box 5)
  - BZA farewell to Lone Kelley, Annandale HS Symphony Band, Senior Citizens Recognition Awards, Salvation Army, 1976 May 17 (Box 5)
  - Persia Henry of Springfield congratulated by Board for saving life, 1976 May 17 (Box 5)
  - Concorde Protest - 3 "lanterns" in Massey Building, 1976 May 18- 1976 May 23 (Box 5)
  - Lorton maps prepared by Mapping, 1976 May 20 (Box 5)
  - Concorde monitored at Dulles for noise with Lee Rud and TV crew, 1976 May 24 (Box 5)
  - Signing of Wiehle Ave. bridge agreement with Gulf Reston, Herrity, Pennino, 1976 May 24 (Box 5)
  - Playmobile at Herndon, Construction on ACCESS, Reston, 1976 May 27 (Box 5)
  - [Unidentified party], 1976 May or June (Box 5)
  - Record shots of Courthouse and lawn monuments, mural for History Branch OCP, 1976 June (Box 5)
  - Jim Pammel, 1976 June (Box 5)